so is AI generated code
secure yeah very broad easy question and
I think that answer based off the
success of your company guy the answer
is
no
90% of the issues that most Enterprises
worry about from a security perspective
is pretty standard stuff right SQL
injection Crosset scripting buffer
overflows thing about llms is the
majority of the time by and large the
most predictable is insecure code
however it absolutely has all the
knowledge of those secure ways too right
you just have to direct it towards that
area and Robin Hood when llms first came
out the head of our absc team at the
time
ran Fest and in one week there was able
to with very high accuracy and
reliability produce real solutions to
these problem s automatically identified
by sneak it was like oh here's the sneak
item write me a safe reliable version of
this and it does fairly accurately with
very high reliability produce the right
bit of code that then can just be
committed as a
PR prompt injection
fundamentally is a problem around
control plane and data plane the data at
which it's analyzed and the commands at
which you tell it are all the same there
is no distinction between the
instructions I'm telling you and the
data to be analyzed and that is the
problem